Cell: 954-254-8417

Summary

Upcoming graduate with a strong background in maintaining computer hardware and software, a keen proficiency in front end web development languages, as well as an introductory understanding of both server-side web scripting and networking technologies. Possesses additional experience in providing exceptional customer experiences, as both a previous customer service representative and customer service department manager.

Education

Broward College • 2022 - Present

Diploma:

Completing an Associate of Science in Software and Web Development (expected graduation in December 2024)

College-Awarded Technical Certifications:

- Web Programming Specialist
- Front-End Web Specialist
- Information Technology Support Specialist

Work Experience

H&R Block • Feb. 2023 - Apr. 2023

Customer Service Personnel (Seasonal)

Oversaw scheduling of tax professional's clientele and provided exceptional customer experiences.

Horizon Health • Oct. 2020 - Apr. 2022

Customer Service Manager

Managed employee relations for the department, tracked and maintained client retention and customer satisfaction for the company, oversaw training of new employees, and was the lead of CSR call quality assurance.

Horizon Health · Sep. 2018 - Oct. 2020

Customer Service Representative

Provided exceptional customer experiences to ensure customer satisfaction and retention.

Skills

Trained in A+, Network+, and Linux+ fundamental concepts, as well as in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and UI/UX design.

Achievements

2023 PlutoHacks Hackathon Winner: https://www.plutohacks.com/2023-highlights/

My team was awarded "Best First Time Hack" in Broward College's "PlutoHacks" hackathon, for having designed a VRbased job interview simulation environment utilizing Unity and ChatGPT.